travelpayouts.com 2018-08-31

# Privacy Policy – Travelpayouts affiliate network

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement explains:

What personal data is collected by the owner of this web site or provided by you, through our interactions with you and your use of our web site (www.travelpayouts.com), apps and software

How your personal data will be used, where it is held, how long it will be kept and your rights.

Please read this privacy policy carefully.

#### **Definitions and interpretation**

In this privacy, the following definitions are used:

**Data controller**  means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed. 

**Data processor** , in relation to personal data, means any person (other than an employee of the data controller) who processes the data on behalf of the data controller.

**“You”, “your”** or “ **data subject”** means: 

\- Visitors to our website

\- Subscribers to any service we offer through our site

-Users of our applications

\- Prospective or existing clients corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise

**Data controller** **,** **“we”** , **“us”** and **“our”** means:

Go Travel Un Limited, its subsidiaries and its data processors;

This Privacy Policy describes our use of Personal identifiable and non-identifiable Information that we collect when you visit or use the Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to (a) the use of your Personal Information that is collected by third parties that we do not does not own or control or that do not support. (b) The collection and use of your Personal Information in connection with our Affiliate Program is governed by our Offer Agreement that is provided upon your registration . 

**Personal data**  means any information relating to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified in particular by reference to an identifier.

This definition provides for a wide range of personal identifiers to constitute personal data, including name, identification number, location data or online identifier, reflecting changes in technology and the way organisations collect information about people. The definition incorporates, where applicable, the definitions provided in General Data Protection Regulation.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically for changes. If you do not accept the amended Policy, please stop using this Website.

#### **Who we are (Identity of the data controller)**  

Go Travel Un Limited, a Hong Kong Corporation, number 1658681, having its registered office at Suite 1504, 15/F, Chinachem Tower, 34-37 Connaught Rd Central, Hong Kong doing business as TravelPayouts, its subsidiaries and its data processors collectively referred to as TravelPayouts), who operate a number of web sites;

#### **Personal data we may collect from you**  

**We may collect and process the following data and personal information about you:**

#### Personal Data you provide us voluntarily 

This information may include your:

Email address and login data

#### **Children**

We do not offer any products or services for purchase by children. If you are under 16, you may use our Website only with the involvement of your holder of parental responsibility. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children below 16 without the consent of the child's holder of parental responsibility.

#### **Information you provide about others**

In providing personal data about other individuals (such as someone in whose name you are registering an account or subscribing to our marketing promotions), you represent that you have notified them of (i) the purposes for which information will be used (ii) the recipients of their personal data and (iii) how they can access and correct the information.  You further represent that You have obtained all necessary consents from them.

**INFORMATION WHICH MAY BE MADE AVAILABLE TO US, OR COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY WITH THE USE OF COOKIES OR ANALYTIC TOOLS**

We might get some information from our visitors by recording how they interact with our Website with the use of cookies, analytics tools or obtain data from third parties.

**TECHNICAL INFORMATION, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION:**

Device and connectivity information such as IP (Internet Protocol) address, unique device identifiers (such as the IMEI for phones), the MAC address of the Device's wireless network interface, or the mobile phone number used by the Device), mobile network information, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile browser you use, time zone setting "Device Information";

Configuration data such as browser type, version and language setting, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions

Details of how you used our Website, such as your search queries. Information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page:

Log information, such as error reports, download errors, any problems you experience using our web site and any phone number used to call our customer service number.

We do not match information collected automatically through cookies and analytics tools with other personally identifiable information you may have provided to us when you registered for our Products or submitted a form through our Website.
